export default [
	{
		id: 1,
		question: "What is the average lifespan of a domestic cat?",
		answers: ["15 years", "8 years", "20 years", "25 years"],
	},
	{
		id: 2,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its wrinkled face?",
		answers: ["Pug", "Beagle", "Dalmatian", "Golden Retriever"],
	},
	{
		id: 3,
		question: "What is the scientific name for the domestic cat?",
		answers: ["Felis catus", "Canis lupus", "Panthera leo", "Vulpes vulpes"],
	},
	{
		id: 4,
		question: "Which breed of cat is known for its lack of fur?",
		answers: ["Sphynx", "Maine Coon", "Persian", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 5,
		question: "What is the most popular dog breed in the United States?",
		answers: ["Labrador Retriever", "Poodle", "German Shepherd", "Bulldog"],
	},
	{
		id: 6,
		question:
			"Which cat breed is known for its blue eyes and Siamese-like appearance?",
		answers: ["Siamese", "Scottish Fold", "Ragdoll", "Abyssinian"],
	},
	{
		id: 7,
		question: "What is the smallest breed of dog?",
		answers: ["Chihuahua", "Dachshund", "Pomeranian", "Yorkshire Terrier"],
	},
	{
		id: 8,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its large size and tufted ears?",
		answers: ["Maine Coon", "Sphynx", "Siamese", "Ragdoll"],
	},
	{
		id: 9,
		question: "How many teeth do adult dogs typically have?",
		answers: ["42", "30", "34", "40"],
	},
	{
		id: 10,
		question: "What is the term for a group of kittens?",
		answers: ["Kindle", "Pride", "Pack", "Herd"],
	},
	{
		id: 11,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for having a black tongue?",
		answers: ["Chow Chow", "Dalmatian", "Shih Tzu", "Cocker Spaniel"],
	},
	{
		id: 12,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its distinctive folded ears?",
		answers: ["Scottish Fold", "Siberian", "Birman", "Balinese"],
	},
	{
		id: 13,
		question: "What is the most common eye color for cats?",
		answers: ["Green", "Blue", "Brown", "Yellow"],
	},
	{
		id: 14,
		question: "Which breed of dog was originally bred for bull-baiting?",
		answers: ["Bulldog", "Poodle", "Beagle", "Collie"],
	},
	{
		id: 15,
		question:
			"Which cat breed is known for its 'wild' appearance and spotted coat?",
		answers: ["Bengal", "Sphynx", "Persian", "Siamese"],
	},
	{
		id: 16,
		question:
			"What is the name of the cat in the famous children's book by Dr. Seuss?",
		answers: ["The Cat in the Hat", "Garfield", "Tom", "Felix"],
	},
	{
		id: 17,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its herding abilities?",
		answers: ["Border Collie", "Chihuahua", "Pug", "Dalmatian"],
	},
	{
		id: 18,
		question: "What is a common allergen found in cat saliva?",
		answers: ["Fel d 1", "Histamine", "Pollen", "Dander"],
	},
	{
		id: 19,
		question:
			"Which dog breed is known for its excellent sense of smell and tracking ability?",
		answers: ["Bloodhound", "Greyhound", "Beagle", "Poodle"],
	},
	{
		id: 20,
		question: "What type of coat does a Persian cat have?",
		answers: ["Long and fluffy", "Short and sleek", "Curly", "Hairless"],
	},
	{
		id: 21,
		question: "What is the term for a group of dogs?",
		answers: ["Pack", "Flock", "Herd", "Swarm"],
	},
	{
		id: 22,
		question:
			"Which breed of dog is known for its distinctive blue-black tongue?",
		answers: ["Chow Chow", "Labrador", "Boxer", "Poodle"],
	},
	{
		id: 23,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for being vocal and sociable?",
		answers: ["Siamese", "Maine Coon", "Sphynx", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 24,
		question: "How many toes do most cats have on their front paws?",
		answers: ["Five", "Four", "Three", "Six"],
	},
	{
		id: 25,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its unique 'bat ears'?",
		answers: ["French Bulldog", "German Shepherd", "Husky", "Cocker Spaniel"],
	},
	{
		id: 26,
		question: "What is the typical gestation period for a cat?",
		answers: ["9 weeks", "6 weeks", "12 weeks", "14 weeks"],
	},
	{
		id: 27,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its agility and intelligence?",
		answers: ["Border Collie", "Bulldog", "Basset Hound", "Pug"],
	},
	{
		id: 28,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its curly fur?",
		answers: ["Devon Rex", "Sphynx", "Maine Coon", "Siamese"],
	},
	{
		id: 29,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its distinctive spots?",
		answers: ["Dalmatian", "Beagle", "Boxer", "Terrier"],
	},
	{
		id: 30,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for having a 'smiling' face?",
		answers: ["British Shorthair", "Abyssinian", "Sphynx", "Ragdoll"],
	},
	{
		id: 31,
		question: "What is the average number of puppies in a litter?",
		answers: ["6", "3", "8", "10"],
	},
	{
		id: 32,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its short legs and long body?",
		answers: ["Dachshund", "Beagle", "Poodle", "Boxer"],
	},
	{
		id: 33,
		question: "What is the typical lifespan of a domestic dog?",
		answers: ["10-13 years", "5-7 years", "14-16 years", "18-20 years"],
	},
	{
		id: 34,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for being hairless?",
		answers: ["Sphynx", "Bengal", "Persian", "Maine Coon"],
	},
	{
		id: 35,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its strong protective instincts?",
		answers: ["German Shepherd", "Poodle", "Chihuahua", "Greyhound"],
	},
	{
		id: 36,
		question: "What is the term for a baby cat?",
		answers: ["Kitten", "Cub", "Pup", "Chick"],
	},
	{
		id: 37,
		question:
			"Which breed of dog is known for its wrinkled face and short snout?",
		answers: ["Bulldog", "Labrador", "Dalmatian", "Poodle"],
	},
	{
		id: 38,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its distinctive 'moustache' pattern?",
		answers: ["Turkish Van", "Maine Coon", "Ragdoll", "Abyssinian"],
	},
	{
		id: 39,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its exceptional swimming ability?",
		answers: ["Labrador Retriever", "Beagle", "Shih Tzu", "Chihuahua"],
	},
	{
		id: 40,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for having extra toes?",
		answers: ["Polydactyl", "Siamese", "Persian", "Sphynx"],
	},
	{
		id: 41,
		question: "What is the term for a group of cats?",
		answers: ["Clowder", "Pack", "Herd", "School"],
	},
	{
		id: 42,
		question:
			"Which breed of dog is known for its keen sense of smell and tracking ability?",
		answers: ["Beagle", "Greyhound", "Dachshund", "Poodle"],
	},
	{
		id: 43,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its 'bobbed' tail?",
		answers: ["Manx", "Persian", "Sphynx", "Ragdoll"],
	},
	{
		id: 44,
		question:
			"Which dog breed is known for its distinctive ridge of hair along its back?",
		answers: ["Rhodesian Ridgeback", "Bulldog", "Beagle", "Boxer"],
	},
	{
		id: 45,
		question:
			"Which breed of cat is known for its affectionate and dog-like behavior?",
		answers: ["Ragdoll", "Siamese", "Persian", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 46,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its exceptional sense of smell?",
		answers: ["Bloodhound", "Poodle", "Chihuahua", "Beagle"],
	},
	{
		id: 47,
		question:
			"Which cat breed is known for its 'wild' appearance and spotted coat?",
		answers: ["Bengal", "Sphynx", "Persian", "Siamese"],
	},
	{
		id: 48,
		question:
			"Which breed of dog is known for its loyalty and protective instincts?",
		answers: ["German Shepherd", "Poodle", "Chihuahua", "Greyhound"],
	},
	{
		id: 49,
		question: "What is the term for a baby dog?",
		answers: ["Puppy", "Kitten", "Cub", "Chick"],
	},
	{
		id: 50,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its strong sense of loyalty?",
		answers: ["Akita", "Poodle", "Beagle", "Chihuahua"],
	},
	{
		id: 51,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its long, fluffy coat?",
		answers: ["Persian", "Sphynx", "Siamese", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 52,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its ability to pull sleds?",
		answers: ["Siberian Husky", "Poodle", "Beagle", "Chihuahua"],
	},
	{
		id: 53,
		question: "What is the term for a male cat?",
		answers: ["Tom", "Queen", "Boar", "Jack"],
	},
	{
		id: 54,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its distinctive curly coat?",
		answers: ["Poodle", "Beagle", "Bulldog", "Dachshund"],
	},
	{
		id: 55,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its distinctive 'ticked' coat?",
		answers: ["Abyssinian", "Sphynx", "Persian", "Siamese"],
	},
	{
		id: 56,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its long, silky coat?",
		answers: ["Yorkshire Terrier", "Beagle", "Poodle", "Boxer"],
	},
	{
		id: 57,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its blue eyes?",
		answers: ["Siamese", "Maine Coon", "Persian", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 58,
		question: "What is the term for a female dog?",
		answers: ["Bitch", "Queen", "Sow", "Doe"],
	},
	{
		id: 59,
		question:
			"Which dog breed is known for its distinctive black-and-white coat?",
		answers: ["Dalmatian", "Beagle", "Poodle", "Chihuahua"],
	},
	{
		id: 60,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its tufted ears and large size?",
		answers: ["Maine Coon", "Sphynx", "Siamese", "Ragdoll"],
	},
	{
		id: 61,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its speed and racing ability?",
		answers: ["Greyhound", "Poodle", "Beagle", "Chihuahua"],
	},
	{
		id: 62,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its distinctive 'bobbed' tail?",
		answers: ["Manx", "Persian", "Sphynx", "Ragdoll"],
	},
	{
		id: 63,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its distinctive blue-black tongue?",
		answers: ["Chow Chow", "Labrador", "Boxer", "Poodle"],
	},
	{
		id: 64,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for being vocal and sociable?",
		answers: ["Siamese", "Maine Coon", "Sphynx", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 65,
		question: "What is the most common eye color for cats?",
		answers: ["Green", "Blue", "Brown", "Yellow"],
	},
	{
		id: 66,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its long, silky coat?",
		answers: ["Yorkshire Terrier", "Beagle", "Poodle", "Boxer"],
	},
	{
		id: 67,
		question:
			"Which cat breed is known for its blue eyes and Siamese-like appearance?",
		answers: ["Siamese", "Scottish Fold", "Ragdoll", "Abyssinian"],
	},
	{
		id: 68,
		question:
			"Which dog breed is known for its excellent sense of smell and tracking ability?",
		answers: ["Bloodhound", "Greyhound", "Beagle", "Poodle"],
	},
	{
		id: 69,
		question: "What type of coat does a Persian cat have?",
		answers: ["Long and fluffy", "Short and sleek", "Curly", "Hairless"],
	},
	{
		id: 70,
		question:
			"Which breed of dog is known for its distinctive ridge of hair along its back?",
		answers: ["Rhodesian Ridgeback", "Bulldog", "Beagle", "Boxer"],
	},
	{
		id: 71,
		question:
			"Which breed of cat is known for its affectionate and dog-like behavior?",
		answers: ["Ragdoll", "Siamese", "Persian", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 72,
		question:
			"Which dog breed is known for its keen sense of smell and tracking ability?",
		answers: ["Beagle", "Greyhound", "Dachshund", "Poodle"],
	},
	{
		id: 73,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its 'bobbed' tail?",
		answers: ["Manx", "Persian", "Sphynx", "Ragdoll"],
	},
	{
		id: 74,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its distinctive curly coat?",
		answers: ["Poodle", "Beagle", "Bulldog", "Dachshund"],
	},
	{
		id: 75,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its distinctive 'ticked' coat?",
		answers: ["Abyssinian", "Sphynx", "Persian", "Siamese"],
	},
	{
		id: 76,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its long, silky coat?",
		answers: ["Yorkshire Terrier", "Beagle", "Poodle", "Boxer"],
	},
	{
		id: 77,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its blue eyes?",
		answers: ["Siamese", "Maine Coon", "Persian", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 78,
		question: "What is the term for a female dog?",
		answers: ["Bitch", "Queen", "Sow", "Doe"],
	},
	{
		id: 79,
		question:
			"Which dog breed is known for its distinctive black-and-white coat?",
		answers: ["Dalmatian", "Beagle", "Poodle", "Chihuahua"],
	},
	{
		id: 80,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its tufted ears and large size?",
		answers: ["Maine Coon", "Sphynx", "Siamese", "Ragdoll"],
	},
	{
		id: 81,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its speed and racing ability?",
		answers: ["Greyhound", "Poodle", "Beagle", "Chihuahua"],
	},
	{
		id: 82,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its distinctive 'bobbed' tail?",
		answers: ["Manx", "Persian", "Sphynx", "Ragdoll"],
	},
	{
		id: 83,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its distinctive blue-black tongue?",
		answers: ["Chow Chow", "Labrador", "Boxer", "Poodle"],
	},
	{
		id: 84,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for being vocal and sociable?",
		answers: ["Siamese", "Maine Coon", "Sphynx", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 85,
		question: "What is the most common eye color for cats?",
		answers: ["Green", "Blue", "Brown", "Yellow"],
	},
	{
		id: 86,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its long, silky coat?",
		answers: ["Yorkshire Terrier", "Beagle", "Poodle", "Boxer"],
	},
	{
		id: 87,
		question:
			"Which cat breed is known for its blue eyes and Siamese-like appearance?",
		answers: ["Siamese", "Scottish Fold", "Ragdoll", "Abyssinian"],
	},
	{
		id: 88,
		question:
			"Which dog breed is known for its excellent sense of smell and tracking ability?",
		answers: ["Bloodhound", "Greyhound", "Beagle", "Poodle"],
	},
	{
		id: 89,
		question: "What type of coat does a Persian cat have?",
		answers: ["Long and fluffy", "Short and sleek", "Curly", "Hairless"],
	},
	{
		id: 90,
		question:
			"Which breed of dog is known for its distinctive ridge of hair along its back?",
		answers: ["Rhodesian Ridgeback", "Bulldog", "Beagle", "Boxer"],
	},
	{
		id: 91,
		question:
			"Which breed of cat is known for its affectionate and dog-like behavior?",
		answers: ["Ragdoll", "Siamese", "Persian", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 92,
		question:
			"Which dog breed is known for its keen sense of smell and tracking ability?",
		answers: ["Beagle", "Greyhound", "Dachshund", "Poodle"],
	},
	{
		id: 93,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its 'bobbed' tail?",
		answers: ["Manx", "Persian", "Sphynx", "Ragdoll"],
	},
	{
		id: 94,
		question: "Which dog breed is known for its distinctive curly coat?",
		answers: ["Poodle", "Beagle", "Bulldog", "Dachshund"],
	},
	{
		id: 95,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its distinctive 'ticked' coat?",
		answers: ["Abyssinian", "Sphynx", "Persian", "Siamese"],
	},
	{
		id: 96,
		question: "Which breed of dog is known for its long, silky coat?",
		answers: ["Yorkshire Terrier", "Beagle", "Poodle", "Boxer"],
	},
	{
		id: 97,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its blue eyes?",
		answers: ["Siamese", "Maine Coon", "Persian", "Bengal"],
	},
	{
		id: 98,
		question: "What is the term for a female dog?",
		answers: ["Bitch", "Queen", "Sow", "Doe"],
	},
	{
		id: 99,
		question:
			"Which dog breed is known for its distinctive black-and-white coat?",
		answers: ["Dalmatian", "Beagle", "Poodle", "Chihuahua"],
	},
	{
		id: 100,
		question: "Which cat breed is known for its tufted ears and large size?",
		answers: ["Maine Coon", "Sphynx", "Siamese", "Ragdoll"],
	},
];
